# Valeri Zanguri

zanguraa@gmail.com • Valeri on linkedin • (+995) 591 926 322 • Tbilisi, Gergia

#### About me

Hey, I am a Web and Mobile developer. I have have experience working with real projects (next js, Remix js, react native, svelte.js etc). I always seek out new challenges, I love solving problems and never give up. I devote all my time to programming and building projects using tech I love.

## My Projects

- Soniq [Next js, styled-components] Real project www.soniq.tech
- Volocopter [Remix js, styled-components] Real project Volocopter.com
- Check my all repositories here My github

# Work Experience

#### Freesy - startup company

Remote

React Native Developer

April, 2023 - present

 Dedicated React Native developer specializing in restaurant food purchasing apps at Freesy company. Crafting seamless mobile experiences by leveraging React Native's power and versatility to enhance the way customers order and enjoy food.

## Pepup - startup company

Remote

Full-stack web - Mobile Developer

September, 2022 - April 2023

• Experienced developer at PepUp startup, leading API and frontend development. Spearheaded creation of APIs and web frontends, while driving React Native app development with Styled Components. Proficiently utilized Node.js and MongoDB for backend, and React for frontend implementation.

## Bitcamp - Full Stack Web Developer course

Tbilisi, Georgia

Mentor

September 2022 - 2023

• We help new people who want to learn web development, we share our experience and at the same time deepen our knowledge.

Credo Bank

Tbilisi, Georgia

IT Support

October 2015 - Present

• Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers, and scanners.

## The tech I love

**Tech Stack:** JavaScript, Csharp, ASP.NET, React, Svelte.js, Typescript, Next.js, React-native, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Node.js(b), PostgreSQL, Linux, , Styled-components, Bootstrap, HTML, Tailwind CSS, Git, GitHub, Flutter, Dart, Figma, AdobeXD

**Languages:** English [conversant], Georgian [native].

#### **Certificates**

Full-stack Course - PRO, React, React Native, React Redux, Redux Toolkit, Redux Fundamentals, React App, Node js, Typescript, Bootstrap, Css, HTML, Javascript - Vuejs, Csharp, Csharp - udemy,

**Languages:** English [conversant], Georgian [native].

## **Education**

Bitcamp

*Intensive full stack web development bootcamp.* 

**Grena Academy** 

Network Administrator - Cisco systems - CCNA v5.0.

Georgia Technical University

Bachelor's Degree in Energy and Electrical Engineering.

Tbilisi, Georgia

2022 - 2023, jan 1 **Tbilisi, Georgia** 

2014 - 2015

Tbilisi, Georgia

2010 - 2014